If everyone's life had a genre,
what would yours be?
Film noir, with its murky underworld?
A thriller driven by hidden crimes?
Or a romantic comedy?
What's the order, sir?
Whatever the genre,
I'm sure everyone's lives are interesting.
But why did mine have to be this one?
You have amnesia.
You have a textbook case
of dissociative amnesia,
meaning you've forgotten
key autobiographical details
such as your name, age, or occupation.
It's the same amnesia
you often see in dramas and movies.
Exactly.
-Sorry?
-This…
It's actually possible?
How can I not remember a single thing?
It's not as common
as you see in dramas, but--
And what normally happens in dramas?
Well, they usually wake up,
turn to the person beside them,
and ask with a vacant, innocent look,
"Who are you?"
Something like that.
And where are they?
The person I'm supposed to ask
"Who are you?" with an innocent look?
Unfortunately, there is no one.
No one?
You were unconscious
when you were brought in two weeks ago.
You were found alone,
collapsed on the ground,
and your body displayed
multiple signs of injury.
And we couldn't use your fingerprints
to identify you, so…
What the heck?
When you were found,
your fingerprints were damaged.
Without fingerprints,
we were unable to identify you,
so we had no way
of contacting your family.
Then shouldn't there have been
an investigation?
The police tried to investigate
what happened,
but you were found on a remote road
with no CCTV cameras.
And they didn't find
any viable fingerprints
on the clothes and shoes you were wearing
when you were found.
Okay, hold up.
So, in a nutshell,
I was found on the road and brought here
two weeks ago.
You couldn't identify me.
The accident investigation was a bust.
And I lost my memory?
That's a perfect summary.
Then what should I do now?
It would be great
if your memory returned--
What if it doesn't?
If it doesn't?
You'll be classified as
an unidentified person,
and once you've been treated,
you'll be sent to a government facility.
So, put simply,
I'm in a damn sticky mess.
You really are excellent at summarizing.
That's a good sign.
OUR STICKY LOVE
Who are you?
How did you end up here
after such a terrible accident?
How is it possible that you don't even
remember your own name?
But…
you're pretty.
Check out this body.
Abs? Why do you have abs?
I must say, at first glance,
I really like what I see.
With these looks,
you should have become a celebrity.
Why didn't you?
If you had, even if you had amnesia,
other people would have recognized you.
Who the heck were you?
Damn it, who the heck was I?
Oh, come on!
SANDEUL HOSPITAL
ONE WEEK LATER
Nowadays,
government-run facilities aren't half bad.
That's right.
I hear they even educate
North Korean refugees
and help them find jobs.
Think of it as an opportunity
to start life anew.
Go there and try to find
what you're good at.
You scared me.
Okay, let's try whatever.
I lost my memory due to a head injury,
so if I stimulate it again,
maybe it will come back.
That's it. Attagirl.
She's got her pep back.
Fancy some peanuts?
Good heavens!
-Oh no!
-Goodness, dear.
Oh my.
Looks like she's coming to.
You should dial down the crazy.
Why would you smash your noggin
into the wall like that?
Or you should've waited an hour to do it.
Sorry?
Shortly after you passed out,
someone came by.
Your boyfriend.
Someone who actually knows you
finally came for you!
Really?
Apparently, your boyfriend's been
looking for you like crazy.
He has?
And where is he?
-My so-called boyfriend?
-Hold your horses. He'll be here soon.
Your boyfriend's a strapping young man.
A total looker.
I thought he was an actor.
Aren't you lucky?
He was totally my type.
Thank God.
Of course.
Looking this good,
there's no way I'm single.
I can finally find out who I am.
You've been through so much, dear.
I hear someone coming.
Oh my…
I hit the jackpot.
Grandma.
There you are.
This is my grandson.
He's a model.
-Say hello.
-Nice to meet you.
I hear someone else coming.
You heard, didn't you?
That someone came for you.
Shall we call him in?
Come on in.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
Who the heck
is this scruffy, scrappy boxer?
Why is Scrappy standing in front of me?
Go Eun-sae.
You really don't remember anything?
You don't know who I am?
Yes, I'd like to keep it that way.
It's me.
No.
Jang Tae-ha.
Please.
Your boyfriend.
Moving, isn't it?
For three whole weeks,
he says he searched every hospital
in Seoul, Gyeonggi,
and the entire capital area to find you.
I heard he was a looker…
That he looked like an actor…
His shoulders are as broad as a barn door.
-Like a young Baek Il-seob.
-Looks like Park Geun-hyeong to me.
That's exactly how Park looked
when he was young.
So, in a nutshell,
my name is Go Eun-sae.
As for age,
I'm 33 years old.
I work part-time at a taffy shop,
making taffy,
and I've been dating you,
a boxing coach, for two years,
and we live together,
even looking to get married soon?
Well, what to do?
I don't believe any of that.
For starters, how could I not have
a proper job at 33?
You were an aspiring web novel writer
who never made it.
So you started working at
my grandmother's taffy shop a month ago.
Then do you have any proof
that we're dating?
Hey, come on.
This couldn't possibly be proof
that we're dating.
This could be two tourists passing by
who happened to be snapped together.
Any other photos?
-This is the only one.
-See?
How is that possible
when we dated for two years?
I lost my phone while running around
looking for you these past three weeks.
-It had all our photos.
-You expect me to believe that?
It would've helped
if we had your phone,
but, as you know,
they found you with nothing.
I have no clue what happened to you
after you went out to meet a friend,
but for now,
I'm just glad you're alive.
Do you
usually not wash up?
Oh, I…
Well, my car broke down on the way here,
so I had to fix it in a hurry.
And you don't shave?
Shave?
It's been a bit hectic recently.
Fine, I get it.
Can you just reach out
to my family for me?
You don't have any.
I don't have any?
You grew up in an orphanage.
Hold on.
So I don't have any family,
I lost my phone,
so I don't have any friends' numbers,
and I'm an aspiring web novel writer,
so I don't have any colleagues.
So, in other words,
you're the only one I have
in the whole world?
Is that right?
As I said,
you're excellent at summarizing.
If you're done talking, you can go home.
You can get the rest of your treatment
as an outpatient.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure, yes.
You should go wash your face or something.
How can you just believe he's my boyfriend
and let him take me home?
We checked with the police,
and the person he's been looking for
matched your description perfectly.
He even knew about
the triangle of moles on your butt.
He got it exactly right.
Moles on my butt?
Yes, we all saw them
when we were treating you.
Just here on your right butt cheek,
you have a triangle of moles.
And the mole at the very top
is a little different in color.
Greenish, if you will.
He even got that right.
Quite frankly,
those sorts of details are things
only a boyfriend would know.
Even so, how could you let me go
with a complete stranger--
If you don't believe him,
you can refuse to go with him.
You can wait here for the police
to escort you to a government facility.
It's true. They're in a triangle,
and one's a different color.
So,
everything that guy said is true?
Okay, I'll go with him for now.
Who knows? Maybe going back
to where I lived will jog my memory.
I used to wear this?
I really wore something so tacky?
You have to take these three times a week…
I mean, three times a day.
So what now?
Do we go home?
Yeah.
Wait.
Why are we going there, not Seoul?
We don't live in Seoul.
Don't be ridiculous.
I may not remember who I am,
but I remember
the Seoul subway map up to Line 9.
We used to live in Seoul,
but we moved to Gujin two months ago.
We… What?
Where the heck is Gujin?
My hometown.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
GUJIN TAFFY VILLAGE
The rice came out perfect!
Come on, you can do better.
-Isn't the rice good?
-Tae-ha, you're back?
Yes, ma'am.
Careful, now.
GUJIN-GUN TRADITIONAL RICE TAFFY
Hello.
-Hey.
-Hi!
-Must be her.
-That her?
What the…
Who are those rough-looking women?
If I knew I'd be lucky enough
to see your face today,
I would've worn my glasses.
This is her, isn't it?
Your future missus
who came from Seoul with you?
Yes.
Say hello. They're from this village.
Do you know me?
Why, are you famous or something?
-How would we know you?
-You don't?
Never seen me around?
Apparently I live here.
Well, that's the thing, isn't it?
You came here almost two months ago,
but it's the first time you've graced us.
So how could we have seen you?
I apologize. We've had a lot going on.
I'll tell you the details later.
-Sure.
-You do that.
You can get going now.
You're in my way.
I'll get going…
so move out of my way.
Tae-ha,
what's with her?
Tae-ha.
She's…
Oh boy, Tae-ha.
Wow, what a character.
That one's no ordinary girl, is she?
Definitely not.
She's clearly one of those rude Gen Z kids
who left their manners behind.
She and I will never get along,
not in a million years.
-Hello, I'm--
-Song-wol.
I told you, right?
She doesn't remember anything.
Do you know me? Did I really work here?
And what about him?
Is he really my boyfriend?
Please tell me everything
you know about me.
Come on, just tell me.
You don't have to worry about him.
She can't speak. She has aphasia.
Her name is Kim Song-wol,
and she's from North Korea.
She can't speak,
but she can hear and read just fine,
so communication isn't a problem.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, did I really--
Keep it down, old lady!
Go outside and choke on some taffy.
What did you just say?
My grandma has dementia.
She didn't mean to be rude--
No, not that.
"Old lady"?
Why would you call me an old lady?
Why would you call me old?
If you're going to be that darn loud,
you should've become a singer.
Goodness, you're hurting my ears.
Honey, take this old lady outside.
What a crazy bitch.
One has dementia,
and the other has aphasia.
There's really no one I can ask?
Let's go home now.
You should get some rest.
By "home," you mean the house
we used to live in, right?
This is our home.
Well…
Hold up.
Wait a minute.
Why's it barking at me?
If I used to live here,
it should run over, wagging its tail.
Why is it barking at me
like I'm a complete stranger?
It's not our dog.
It was in there.
That's village dogs for you.
They wander around
and eat and sleep
if they find a doghouse they fancy.
It's been staying here the past few days.
Are you serious?
Thankfully, it doesn't bark for long.
It stops after a few barks.
This is killing me.
That makes no sense.
Flowers, flowers, flowers, and flowers.
Flowers everywhere.
Has this blanket been in the family
for three generations or something?
-It was bought recently--
-No way someone paid money for this.
What's with this bed?
How very old-school soap opera.
Is this chicken soup?
Why is there reishi mushroom in lotion?
This was really expensive…
I'm sure of it.
I didn't live here.
Why do you think that?
Because I don't like a single thing
in this house.
You hated superficial things,
so we didn't renovate when we moved in--
I'm the girl who cropped my hospital gown.
You're saying I hated superficial things
when I loved to get dolled up?
And how come there's none of your stuff
in the bedroom?
If we were due to get married,
we must have shared a room.
When I found out the state you were in,
I moved all of my stuff there.
For you, it'd be like
sleeping with a man you just met.
It would be strange.
-So you were being considerate?
-Yes.
Your name's Jang Tae-ha, right?
Mr. Jang Tae-ha.
Tell me about how we met.
I'm finding it hard to believe
any of this, so start from the beginning.
A blind date?
Or did you make the first move?
I need to know how and why
I ended up living with you.
We met in the mountains.
What are you looking at?
You can continue on your way. I've got it.
Are you freaking kidding me?
I fell for you
just because you caught a toad?
You just wouldn't stop chasing me.
Whoa, wait. What did you say?
I pursued you? Not the other way around?
You said you'd kill yourself
if I didn't go out with you, so I did.
One day, you showed up with your stuff,
so we started living together.
You insisted you couldn't live without me,
so we decided to get married.
Wait. Hold it right there.
Look, Mr. Jang Tae-ha.
Just because I don't remember anything
doesn't mean you can just make things up.
I haven't believed
anything you've said so far,
and this is by far the most unbelievable.
Should I go on?
No, thank you.
Are you trying to give me a heart attack?
Then get some rest. I'll be right back
after returning the car to the gym.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
All right, good!
One more time.
One-two! Again.
Again, one-two!
Good!
What's wrong?
Your shirt's still half dry.
Get up.
On your feet!
Enough for today.
Thank you, sir.
The more you sweat during training,
the less you bleed during a match.
I'll sweat buckets tomorrow.
If you say so.
There you are.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Coach.
Good work, Pil-seung.
-Sir, I'll be going now.
-Okay.
-Go on.
-Okay. Goodbye.
-Hey, run all the way home.
-Yes, sir!
Hey, how did it go?
Did you bring her back okay?
She doesn't seem to believe me.
Figures.
She must be used to
living in luxury in Seoul.
Something inside her
must be resisting the countryside.
Do you think
it'll be okay?
We can't get caught, no matter what.
3 WEEKS AGO
This is a reserved space,
so you can't park here. Please move.
-You must be new here.
-Sorry?
Yes. You must frequent
the Prosecutors' Office
to notice a change in security detail.
I have, for about three years now.
I changed my car over the weekend,
so it's not registered yet.
-But this is my parking space.
-Sorry?
And I'll continue to frequent this place,
so please remember my face.
I'm Prosecutor Go Ji-won
from the Anti-Corruption Department.
And this here is our top gun,
Prosecutor Go Ji-won.
You saw her at the inauguration, right?
Yes. How could I forget someone
with such a unique presence?
I have many other
exceptional qualities, Chief.
You'll see them soon in my work.
If you'll excuse me…
Mr. Mayor, this is my girlfriend.
Hello, I'm Go Ji-won
from the Prosecutors' Office.
Yes, I've heard a lot about you.
An anti-corruption prosecutor, correct?
Anti-corruption?
You must be one of the elite.
This is Chairman Baek Sang-gil
of Mirae Eden Company.
I'm well aware.
I found your guest introduction
rather memorable.
It's nice to meet you.
I'll leave you to it, then.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
The mayor and Chairman Baek will leave
the venue between 10:00 and 10:10.
I'm only escorting the mayor to the venue.
The official plan is that
the mayor's driver will take him home.
But instead of going home,
he'll be making contact?
Don't worry.
This is valuable intel
my aide boyfriend managed to get me.
I have to make this work.
You'll have to wait a bit longer
for the final decision on the contractor
for the Irang-dong project.
There are a lot of eyes on this,
so it's hard to speed things up.
Before we bring the thunder,
it'd be best for you
to take care of it swiftly.
We wouldn't want the thunder
to be followed by a downpour,
leaving our dear mayor's
royal robes be drenched, would we now?
You'll have to wait a bit longer
for the final decision on the contractor
for the Irang-dong project.
We meet again, Prosecutor.
Looks like it.
Though not in the most dignified place.
We only got word of your visit
at the last second,
so we ended up showing you
an unseemly side.
Given the chance to make it up to you,
we'd treat you handsomely.
As for your watch…
we'd replace it quite generously.
I guess you think
prosecutors in Korea are a joke.
I'm loaded.
I don't need your dirty money to get by.
If you're waiting for your investigators,
my men have gone to greet them,
so no need to worry too much.
So, Prosecutor,
what will you do now?
Crazy bastard.
Seriously?
You bastards want to…
Hey!
What the…
You know,
I don't really watch movies anymore.
The ending's already decided,
and wasting all that time
just to watch it unfold…
seems fucking stupid.
I'm saying, don't even bother.
Hey! Get over here, damn it!
Fuck!
You'll have to wait a bit longer
for the final decision on the contractor
for the Irang-dong project.
There are a lot of eyes on this,
so it's hard to speed things up.
What should we do now?
NARITA, TOKYO
LANDED
I got the sales report.
Thanks to you, Director Jang,
the Tokyo pachinko business
is faring well.
Not at all.
Tae-ha.
Yes, sir?
You told me recently
that you wanted
to leave this world behind.
You may leave.
Sir?
You're the one who turned Geukrakpa,
some back-alley gang, into Mirae Eden.
You deserve that much.
Sir.
Just do one last job for me
before you leave.
We need to take care of a prosecutor.
It is a prosecutor we're talking about,
so things could get messy.
I need someone I can trust.
Think of it as giving me a parting gift.
Tae-ha.
Can you do it for me?
Current condition?
Almost out.
What's the order, sir?
-Forget it.
-Sorry?
Chairman Baek asked me
to take care of this myself.
Don't get your hands dirty.
I'll do it myself.
HONG DO-YEOP
I need your help.
I have to save someone.
I'm certain Baek Sang-gil will scrutinize
every step of the process,
illegally securing traffic CCTV footage
if necessary.
Fortunately, there is exactly one place
on the way to the final destination
that's a CCTV blind spot.
Okay.
I assume you didn't leave any crumbs.
Yes, sir.
Good work.
SANDEUL HOSPITAL
How could this happen?
She finally woke up after two weeks…
UNKNOWN, F, 20S
…but she has amnesia.
Since she has no fingerprints,
she'll be listed as unidentified
and placed in a government facility.
Wouldn't that be too risky?
She must be kept from the outside world.
In this situation,
it'd be safest to keep her by your side.
But to do that, you would need to have
a valid reason to take her home.
If you were family, for example.
Or someone who is to become family,
like a fiancé.
The doctor said it's probably
a temporary aftereffect of the accident.
Surely her memory will come back
once she recovers.
By the way,
have you found a stowaway boat for Japan?
Kaito is looking for local brokers.
Okay, good.
Once her memory comes back
and the boat's ready, we'll send her off.
Then it'll all be over.
Until then, we have to keep her here.
So just bite the bullet.
Pretend to be her boyfriend for a while.
Okay.
Hey, don't worry too much.
We're in the middle of nowhere,
the kind of backwater
where nothing's changed in years.
There's no place safer than this.
No matter how I look at it,
it's too unfamiliar.
Just because I lost my memory,
it doesn't mean I lost my intuition.
How can every corner of the house,
every last spoon, feel so unfamiliar?
Come on.
If only these were fine.
I wouldn't be this frustrated. Seriously.
Just what kind of accident did I get into?
What's that? Is that…
What are you doing?
Did you get
your memory back?
Why?
Are you scared I might
get it back?
Unfortunately, my memory hasn't come back,
but I did see something.
I found this in the yard.
You said I fell for you
because you caught one for me,
but I'm not scared of it at all.
I could even keep it as a pet.
Hey, can you…
What's going on?
I guess you lost your fear
with your memory.
Don't be ridiculous.
The doctor said head injuries
can cause all sorts of aftereffects.
You're not my boyfriend, are you?
I am.
Still going with that story?
I am your boyfriend.
Is that right?
Did you say we dated for two years?
Yeah.
And we've been living together
since we were in Seoul?
-Yeah.
-Let's say I did pursue you.
You must have liked me back
if you agreed to live with me.
Yeah.
Then you won't mind this.
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi